## VANSHIKA SHARMA

NORTH YORK, ON M2J 1Z4 | 647 894 3730 | vanshikasharma37303@gmail.com

### **Summary**

Highly ambitious and experienced customer service representative with retail expertise. Proven ability to provide excellent customer service, establish strong connections with customers, and surpass sales targets. Strong communication and problem-solving abilities, with a strong emphasis on teamwork and collaboration.

#### Skills

- · Strong communication and interpersonal skills
- Customer Service and sales experience
- · Excellent problem-solving skills
- · Ability to work well under pressure

- · Strong attention to detail
- · Knowledge of sales techniques and strategies
- · Technical assistance

### **Experience**

Sales Associate 11/2021 to 03/2022 Expression London India, Punjab

- Helped customers find specific products, answered questions and offered product advice.
- Worked with fellow sales team members to achieve group targets.
- Trained new team members in cash register operation, stock procedures and customer services.

# Customer Service Representative The BRICK

06/2022 to Current North York, ON

- Provided exceptional customer service to a diverse clientele, ensuing a positive experience
- · Consistently exceeded sales targets through effective sales techniques and strategies
- Resolved complaints and escalated concerns as necessary to ensure customer satisfaction.
- Trained and mentored new employees, ensuring they were able to provide high-quality customer service.

Student Ambassador
Seneca College
North York, ON

- Conducting campus tours and showcasing facilities and amenities to prospective students and families.
- Participating in open houses, orientations, and recruitment events.
- Providing information and answering questions about academic programs admission requirements, scholarships, and financial aid.

Coordinator 04/2023 to 05/2024
Seneca Student Federation 1750 Finch Ave E

- Oversaw safe, welcoming and highly multicultural environment open to students.
- · Organized and supervised student intramural and recreation programs.
- · Collaborated with teachers to understand and improve classroom conditions.

#### **Education and Training**

**Diploma: Computer Programming and Analysis** Seneca College of Applied Arts and Technology Expected in 12/2024 North York, ON